

Jefri Danil

Jl asam baris Kebon Baru, Tebet JAKARTA SELATAN 081283650292 https://jfridanil.github.io/jefridanil02.github.io/ @jefridanilok24@gmail.com

Results-oriented IT expert with over a year of experience, focused on the digital world using marketing solutions, effective business management to drive sales growth and increase clients' brand equity.

Educational Background

Pamulang University Tangerang Selatan Degree in Informatics Engineering 2022 - now

Work Experience

Admin report
Ninja Express
March 2021 - December 2021
Already accustomed to using Microsoft in work operations.

IT support
PT Secure Packatama
December 2021 - now
Have some understanding of the software.

Skills & Proficiencies

- Usually use HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT programming languages
- Web design using figma

Training and Certificates

Big Data Analysis For Cyber Security In National Data Security System October 2022

The Power Of Artificial Intellegence System For Brings Indonesia To Industry 5.0

March 2023

Jefri Danil

Jl asam baris Kebon Baru, Tebet JAKARTA SELATAN 081283650292 https://jfridanil.github.io/jefridanil02.github.io/, @jefridanilok24@gmail.com

Dear Sir/Madam Tebet, South Jakarta, 12190

Dear Mr/Mrs,

Based on the information I received from one of the job search platforms, your company is currently opening IT vacancies that focus on software and I am very interested in this job.

My educational background is a Bachelor of Information Engineering, Pamulang University. I had a lot of practical experience and exposure during my studies. I have been exposed to various skills that allow me to blend into your company.

From your vacancy, I can see that you are looking for candidates who have superior skills relevant for the digital world. I have knowledge about digital-based business, a little about UI/UX design as well as very good interpersonal and communication skills. So, I think the job description for this position is in accordance with my latest education.

Along with the application letter, I have attached the documents; Curriculum vitae, final diploma, and health certificate for your full consideration. Feel free to contact me via email at jefridanilok@gmail.com if you have any further questions. I appreciate you taking the time to review my application, and I sincerely hope to have the opportunity to move on to the next stage and make a positive contribution to your company.

That's how I actually wrote this job application letter. Thank you for your attention.

Yours faithfully, Jefri Danil